[
{
"ques_no": "1",
"question": "Paragraph tag ?",
"a": "<pg>",
"b": "<para>",
"c": "<p>",
"d": "<text>",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "2",
"question": "Line break tag ?",
"a": "<lb>",
"b": "<br>",
"c": "<line>",
"d": "<bk>",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "3",
"question": "Image tag ?",
"a": "<pic>",
"b": "<img>",
"c": "<image>",
"d": "<src>",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "b"
},
{
"ques_no": "4",
"question": "Bold text tag ?",
"a": "<stronger>",
"b": "<bold>",
"c": "<b>",
"d": "<bt>",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "5",
"question": "Link tag ?",
"a": "<p>",
"b": "<link>",
"c": "<href>",
"d": "<url>",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "a"
},
{
"ques_no": "6",
"question": "Largest heading tag ?",
"a": "<h6>",
"b": "<h1>",
"c": "<h4>",
"d": "<head>",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "2"
},
{
"ques_no": "7",
"question": "Title tag ?",
"a": "<page>",
"b": "<meta>",
"c": "<head>",
"d": "<title>",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "8",
"question": "Ordered list tag ?",
"a": "<ul>",
"b": "<list>",
"c": "<ol>",
"d": "<li>",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "c"
},
{
"ques_no": "9",
"question": "Which tag adds a buttom ?",
"a": "<submit>",
"b": "<press>",
"c": "<click>",
"d": "<button>",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
},
{
"ques_no": "10",
"question": "What does <ul> stand for ?",
"a": "Upper list",
"b": "Underrlined List",
"c": "User list",
"d": "Unordered list",
"answer":"e",
"correct": "d"
}
]